**50% OFF** Annual Plan

EARLY BLACK FRIDAY flash Sale

01 HR 12 Min 32 Sec

Privacy Policy
--------------

This policy describes how we hold and process your private information. It applies to the services Tweetails, TweetDownload and TweetDelete that are operated by TD Social LLC.

Overview
--------

We collect the minimum amount of personal information necessary for our services to function. This is processed with your consent, or on another legal basis. We don't sell any information to third parties, and we only use it as this privacy policy describes.

What information we collect and why
-----------------------------------

We collect various information related to your Twitter account from users who sign in to our website, such as your Twitter user ID, Twitter screen name, and access keys for the Twitter API.  
_Why we collect this:_ We need these details for our Twitter related services to function, and so that we can use Twitter API functions on your behalf in order to provide our services on your Twitter account.

We collect or process certain additional data contained in your Twitter account (which could potentially contain sensitive data) where the functionality our service is providing requires it. This could include your tweets or your direct messages.  
_Why we collect this:_ We only collect this type of data in order to provide a service you've asked us to. We're careful to only hold it for as long as necessary. For example TweetDelete needs to scan your tweets to work out which to delete, but they are normally used temporarily and are not stored in our database. Certain premium functionality does require storing tweets, for example when you have excluded certain tweets from deletion, or if you've uploaded a Twitter data file (those are automatically removed after 3 days).

We collect various information about visitors to our website due to our use of common internet technologies such as web server logs. This includes details like the visitor's browser type, language preference, referring site, additional websites requested, and the date and time of each visitor request. We also collect potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses.  
_Why we collect this:_ We collect this information to understand how visitors use our websites, and to monitor and protect the security and stability of our websites.

For paid services only, we collect related information such as payment amounts, times and currencies, and information related to customers, such as their names and addresses.  
_Why we collect this:_ We collect this information to validate and secure payments. We also have a legal obligation to keep certain data e.g. for tax calculation purposes. We don't collect sensitive details such as credit card numbers (these are handled by our payment processor).

We do not intentionally collect sensitive categories of data. Because we process social media posts, there are situations where such data may pass through our service without our knowledge.

How we share the information we collect
---------------------------------------

We do not sell any information to third parties. We do not share any information with third parties unless a service you've requested necessitates this (for example if you want to share your results page on Tweetails).

Global privacy practices
------------------------

We store and process the information that we collect in the United Kingdom in accordance with this privacy policy. All data is processed fairly and lawfully in accordance with UK and EU law and the principles and requirements of the General Data Protection Regulation (EU) 2016/679 ("the GDPR").

Our legal basis for processing information
------------------------------------------

We only process personal data for lawful purposes as described in Article 6 of the GDPR. For all of the main functionality of our services our legal basis is that you've given us consent to access this information in order to provide a particular service related to your Twitter account.

Generally, the remainder of the processing of personal data we perform is necessary for the purposes of our legitimate interests. For example, the information stored by us in web server logs is necessary for us to monitor the security and stability of our websites.

Right of access
---------------

You have a right to view any data associated with you that we hold. Please visit this page when signed in to our service and you'll see a button here allowing you to view all stored data related to your account.

Right to erasure
----------------

You have a right to request the erasure of any data associated with you that we hold. Please visit this page when signed in to our service and you'll see a button here allowing you to remove your TweetDelete account and all associated data.

Contacting us
-------------

For any matters related to data protection, you can contact us via email to [support@tweetdelete.net](mailto:support@tweetdelete.net) or write to TD Social LLC, 2261 Market Street #4811, San Francisco, California 94114, United States. For any specific data access/deletion requests, please include your Twitter account name.

If we've missed anything or if you have any questions or concerns, please get in touch. We're a small company, but we take user privacy very seriously.

Delete Your Tweets.  
Clean Up Your Twitter Feed on X.

© 2024 TweetDelete . All Rights Reserved
